

GULTEN ULUKAL YONKUC

gulten.ulukal@gmail.com +905307626681

Kadikoy – ISTANBUL

https://github.com/gltnlkl

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I will be moving to Berlin with a blue card (permitted to work) at March.I am a Software Developer following a 12 years career as an architect. My experience in the construction industry instilled in me strong interpersonal, customer service skills and using different Technology solutions with multidisciplinary coordination.

In my personal life, I am early adapter, and fast learner with strong time management and multitasking skills. I am a goal-oriented person, that loves challenges. I have highly motivated strong problem-solving and strategizing skills, which I use to successfully accomplish these goals.

Technologies: Java | Spring-Boot|Spring-Cloud|JavaScript | HTML | CSS | MVC | SQL | postgreSQL | MongoDB | React | Next.js | Git | GitHub

EDUCATION

Bilge Adam Academy

Full-Stack Java Development Boot Camp 2020 – 2021

Mimar Sinan Fine Art University (MSGSU) 2006 - 2010 Faculty of Architecture / Department of Architecture

Eskisehir Anatolian High School (EAL)

2002 - 2006

Science Department

WORK EXPERIENCE

BilgeAdam Teknoloji

Java Software Developer

09.2021 - Present

- •Java Backend applications written in Java 8-16 on the Spring Boot framework and JPA/Hibernate.
- Experience with SQL and relational databases , Docker, Kubernetes technologies and Agile (Scrum) software development methodologies.
- •Write and deploy reusable, well structured and documented code and working with Git.
- •Using of OOP principles & design patterns & Unit Testing.

GHAFARI Associates LLC

Senior Architect

2018 - 2020

- •Leading the assigned international projects, team, customer, and outsources.
- Coordination and integration of civil/electrical/mechanics/it/ structural disciplines.
- Designing and detailing of projects according to the customer needs.

ÇELİK ÇİZGİ Mimarlık İnş. Sn. Tic. Ltd. Şti.

Senior Architecture Team Leader

2010 - 2018

- Responsible for managing design and technical application and construction control of the retail brand.
- Management technical teams on site and creating progress payments and bid documents.
- Managing and integration of civil/electrical/mechanics/it/ structural disciplines.

QUALIFICATIONS

Java, Spring-Boot, Spring-Cloud, Spring-AWS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MVC, SQL, postgreSQL, MySql, MongoDB, React, Next.js, Git, GitHub, Maven, Gradle, Lombok

LANGUAGE

English (Professional Proficiency)

REFERENCES

Bahadır Kaan Öztutam - Bilge Adam Teknoloji - Academy Director Babür Somer - Bilge Adam Teknoloji - Java Boost Senior Trainer